{
    "subject": "resource/The_Starting_Line",
    "predicate": "property/background",
    "object": "group_or_band",
    "human_readable": "The background of The Starting Line is a group or band.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8905165195465088,
            "question": "Is 'The Starting Line' a solo artist or a group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5518088340759277,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the music genre associated with 'The Starting Line'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4830262064933777,
            "question": "Where is 'The Starting Line' based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.439071387052536,
            "question": "Are there any notable collaborations involving 'The Starting Line'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4184942841529846,
            "question": "What type of entity is 'The Starting Line'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41211366653442383,
            "question": "Do any members of 'The Starting Line' have solo projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4101409614086151,
            "question": "When did 'The Starting Line' first start making music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34152472019195557,
            "question": "What are some of the key instruments used by 'The Starting Line'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33289816975593567,
            "question": "Has 'The Starting Line' won any awards for their music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19542196393013,
            "question": "What is the name of any famous album released by 'The Starting Line'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The background of The Starting Line is a group or band.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5464_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'The Starting Line' won any awards for their music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5464_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the key instruments used by 'The Starting Line'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5464_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did 'The Starting Line' first start making music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5464_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5464_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5464_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5464_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5464_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5464_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5464_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5464_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5464_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5464_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5464_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents clearly describe The Starting Line as a band.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly describe \"The Starting Line\" as a band formed in 1999, indicating that its background involves being a group."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}